clicksaudit.com 2019-06-15

# ClicksAudit.com

The aim of this Privacy Policy is to inform users of how we collect and use certain information as a result of services provided by ClicksAudit.com (hereinafter “ClicksAudit.com”) to its customers.

## Our business

ClicksAudit.com develops solutions and provides services regarding advertising source validation, user verification, ad delivery, fraud detection, and monetization for publishers and advertisers which appear on websites and applications on mobile phones or other devices connected to the internet. You may interact directly with our servers (for example, when you click on an ad) or indirectly via a website or mobile application that displays an ad of ours or that utilizes our services.

## GDPR

The European Union ("EU") maintains strict privacy laws through General Data Privacy Regulation ("GDPR") and protecting our customer's data is a main concern to ensure that we maintain the required compliance with the governing authorities.

## Purpose of data collection

With each interaction between your device and our servers we collect certain information, which we will describe below. We use this information to validate and verify that the sources or end-users our customers and partners target are actual human users. We also seek to gain an understanding of how those users got our website. We may provide to our customers and partners reports that contain aggregated data (for instance, the number of visits delivered each day, the number of likely human or non-human clicks on validation survey, and so on), in order to analyze trends, and in order to perform fraud detection.

## Information collected

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. We do, however, record and use information that is not personally identifiable, including but not limited to the following:

  * the IP address of your device on the internet, to do geo-targeting, to identify your mobile operator, connection type, and other details;
  * the ‘user agent’ of your browser or application, and other relevant request headers, to help us identify your device type;
  * the date and time of the ad request or interaction;
  * and a unique identifier, such as your device advertising identifier, that enables us not to show you the same ad over and over again.

From our partners, which include businesses, networks, agencies, publishers, and advertisers; we do collect personal information to identify the client to an account. The collection of this information is on a lawful basis, to which consent has been expressly given, and is part of ClicksAudit.com’ normal business practices. These partners will be asked to provide personal information through the contractual process. This information is used to communicate the status of an account or billing and may include, but is not limited to: name, phone number, email address, website name, address and bank details.

## Use of information

We may use this non-personally identifiable information along with our technology in order to block or target advertising and/or score the non-human or fraud risk percentage of an aggregated traffic source.

## Your Data Rights

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), you have a right to (subject to a limited number of exceptions): (i) request access to and rectification or erasure of your personal information; (ii) obtain restriction of processing or to object to processing of your personal information; and (iii) ask for a copy of your personal information to be provided to them, or a third party, in a digital format. You also have the right to lodge a complaint about the processing of your personal information with your local data protection authority in the EEA.

If you are a client, and would like the personal information ClicksAudit.com holds about you to be corrected or updated please contact info@clicksaudit.com. For the deletion and erasure of personal information, email info@clicksaudit.com to begin the process and we will respond to your request within 30 days.

## The Protection of Minors

The website does not knowingly collect any personal information from minors. The personal information of any minor you provide shall be agreed by the minor's parent or guardian in advance. Minor is defined in accordance with the laws applicable to the Privacy Policy.

## Marketing campaigns

We may contact our partners, which include businesses, networks, agencies, publishers, and advertisers; periodically by e-mail to provide information regarding our discounts, products, services and content that may be of interest to you. If applicable law requires that we receive your consent before we send you certain types of marketing communications, we will only send you those types of communications after receiving your consent.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or request to be opted-out of receiving such communications via email to info@clicksaudit.com.

## Changes to privacy policy

ClicksAudit.com is committed to continually examining and reviewing its privacy practices, and may make changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that material changes are made, the Privacy Policy on this website will be changed. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your continued use of the website after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this website, you are accepting the consent and practices described in this policy and terms of use. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this website.

## Questions and concerns:

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, you may contact us:

ClicksAudit.com – info@clicksaudit.com
